[The Demon Hunter's Romance]
[Episode 33]
Sir, here's your pastry.
Thank you.
As a constable,
you're completely weak.
Well, I'm a female constable.
Pastry.
Sir, would you like to look at some fabric?
They're all high-quality fabrics.
[Linglong Cloth Store]
Dear customers,
welcome to our store.
Sir,
you've bought quite a lot.
Are you setting up a new home?
Someone must be newly married, right?
You have a good eye, sir.
You're quite perceptive.
Congratulations, congratulations!
Since you two are newlyweds,
you must use high-quality bedding.
Come, this way please.
Let me introduce to you.
Over here, we have
the finest bedding.
Take a look.
For this fabric,
comfort is the most important thing.
Do you have anything better?
This way.
These are all excellent fabrics.
Please take a look.
Madam, you have such a good taste.
After choosing the fabric...
Take care, both of you.
Welcome back anytime.
I'll take it.
Alright.
Let's go.
May you have a child soon!
Thank you for your hard work.
It's nothing worth mentioning.
I also bought some
medicinal food and supplements.
There are some for you and some for Banxia.
You're a doctor yourself,
you should be able to tell them apart.
Okay.
Alright.
Then we'll head back first.
You two
may recover without worry here.
I left so suddenly last time,
I don't know how much trouble it caused.
I'm worried Wen Jian can't handle it alone.
I'm sorry for being a burden to you all.
Don't say that.
We're all friends here,
there's no need to be so polite.
Banxia is a good girl.
Don't let her suffer any grievances.
I understand.
Form ranks.
Your ears...
How did they heal?
I was confined by the Peerless Bracelet for many years.
Suddenly losing that restriction,
my demon power surged.
Plus, someone was causing trouble in the shadows.
So I couldn't control myself for a while.
But fortunately, during this time,
I've figured out
how to circulate my demon power.
I used what my father once taught me,
the secret technique of the Eight Pillar Sect.
Gradually,
I can control it at will now.
That's good.
This way,
others won't be able to tell you're a demon.
That's much more convenient.
Indeed.
Let's eat.
Is it yummy?
It's delicious.
You're lying.
They don't know how to cook.
How would they know what ingredients to buy?
Next time, I'll have to
go to town myself
to buy some tasty ingredients.
Let me show you my cooking skills.
Then I'll go with you.
Alright.
Xuanye,
that person causing trouble in the shadows you mentioned,
is it your elder brother?
Yes.
Is it the same person
we saw at Chi Xue's grave last time?
Are you scared?
It's not that I'm scared.
It's just that he keeps
coming back again and again.
It seems like he's not just
trying to cause trouble for you.
Is he asking you to go back home?
Are you going to go back?
If I go back,
what about you?
Besides,
I can't bear to leave you.
Alright, don't think too much about it.
Let's eat.
Okay.
Xuanye,
have you thought about how to explain to my parents
when we return to Nanyang?
I'll just tell them the truth.
How can you tell them the truth?
You definitely can't let them know
about your true identity.
Especially,
you can't let my brother know.
Think about it.
My brother's marriage with Manniang
was ruined by me.
If he finds out
that you're also a demon,
it'll cause a huge uproar.
I can already imagine what he'll say.
You're a demon, Manniang is also a demon.
So why can't he be with Manniang
if I can be with you?
But it's definitely different.
Although you're both demons,
Manniang is an evil demon.
She killed people.
No matter what,
you can't marry
a murderer, can you?
But you're different.
You uphold justice and are always willing to help others.
Taking someone like you as a husband
would be a tremendous blessing.
Taking me as a husband?
Marrying off to you.
Marrying off to you works too.
What are you smiling about?
This year,
you're turning nineteen, right?
Why are you bringing that up?
I'm just calculating,
if we have a daughter,
how long would it take
for her to grow up to be like you?
Don't always
treat me like a child.
Besides,
you're not even married yet.
Where did this daughter come from?
Even if we do get married one day
and have a daughter,
she might not look like me at all.
She might take after you instead.
She would be a little panther.
My daughter is a little panther.
Xuanye,
would our child
know demonic spells?
I suppose they would.
Then how would I ever manage her?
What clan do you belong to?
The Mystic Panther Clan.
The Mystic Panther Clan, so that means...
She'll grow a tail,
sharp teeth,
have fur,
and be fierce and strong.
Banxia,
would you feel wronged?
About what?
Being with me,
not knowing if it's a blessing
or a curse.
Overthinking is pointless in most situations.
If we can't change it,
we should choose to accept it.
If we always make things difficult for ourselves,
we'll never get over such hurdles.
Xuanye,
no matter what happens,
it's our fate.
We just need to cherish it
and that's enough.
Alright,
I'll listen to you.
Moreover,
who knows
when will
such a good thing happen?
Let's eat.
Did you catch that panther demon?
I was incompetent, Master.
I let it escape.
Never mind.
This was an unexpected bonus to begin with.
Catch it if you can,
but don't be obsessed if you can't.
Chunmian,
you must remember when you do things,
never waver in your decisions
and have too much greed.
We only need to identify one goal,
hold onto it
tightly, and that's enough.
You're right, Master.
Master,
this is what the panther demon dropped.
The Bone Flute of the Mystic Panther Clan.
This is exactly it.
Chunmian.
You've done a great service.
This Bone Flute
has the power to reveal and confuse the demon clan.
With it,
our plan
will be even more secure.
[Jingguan]
Does it look good?
It looks good.
it's just a bit too big.
Then let's go to town tomorrow to buy another one.
It's getting late.
We should get some rest soon.
You go ahead and rest then.
I'll sleep outside.
Don't do that.
There's not even a spot
to shelter from the wind and rain out there.
I'll fetch some water for you.
♫When you're in love, your smile is like the spring breeze♫
♫Walking beside me, bathed in moonlight♫
♫No need for words, I already feel it♫
♫Dark hair like ink, time stretches on♫
♫When you're in love, you wish this love could last forever♫
♫Leaning in close to whisper softly♫
♫I miss you♫
♫On every moonlit night♫
♫Tenderness ties us together♫
♫Let me take your hand and keep our promise♫
♫You shake my soul and pull at my heartstrings♫
♫If I think this world is beautiful♫
♫It's partly because of the moon♫
♫And mostly because I met you♫
♫When life gets hard♫
♫All I wish for is to stay by your side♫
♫This lingering love♫
♫Is a treasure we both cherish♫
♫When I turn around, you're there♫
♫Right by my side♫
♫When life gets hard♫
♫All I wish for is to stay by your side♫
♫This lingering love♫
♫Is a treasure we both cherish♫
♫When I turn around, you're there♫
♫Right by my side♫
Here.
Where's Sima Lingying?
She didn't come.
It would be too conspicuous if both of us came.
How is Xuanye?
Has he found a place to settle?
Xuanye found a courtyard outside the city.
He's staying there for now.
That's good.
He should focus on recovering first.
He can come back when things settle down.
Why all the sighing?
Isn't Xuanye fine now?
No, you don't understand.
He's been training in martial arts and cultivating with his father since childhood.
After his family's tragic death,
he took up his father's mantle
and became a demon hunter.
Although he's not exactly
obsessed with hating demons,
over the years,
the number of demons he's defeated
is countless.
But now...
Who would have thought he himself is a demon?
I'm just worried
he won't be able to come to terms with it.
Our worrying won't help.
This is his own matter.
He has to figure it out on his own.
You're right.
How's the situation with Lord Geng?
Has he investigated Banxia's disappearance?
If he was going to, he would have done so already.
Our Lord
sees things as clearly as a mirror.
He knows exactly what's going on,
he just doesn't say it out loud.
Lord Geng is a good official,
but this incident
has put him in a difficult position.
You're awake.
Why am I sleeping here?
You're one to talk.
Your wounds haven't fully healed yet.
It's so cold at night.
Why did you go sleep outside?
Luckily, I woke up in the middle of the night
and carried you inside.
Otherwise, what if you caught a cold?
You carried me in?
You're so heavy.
How could I possibly lift you?
Of course I have to
drag you in.
Your wounds definitely haven't healed completely.
Otherwise, when I was dragging you,
why didn't you wake up at all?
Tonight,
you're not allowed to sleep outside again.
Otherwise, I'll get angry.
Okay.
Go wash up quickly
and change your clothes.
I'll go make some food.
Go sit down quickly.
The food will be ready soon.
Last night...
Nothing.
Nothing happened at all.
It probably got chilly last night.
You felt a bit cold,
so you transformed back into your beast form.
You came inside, found a warm spot,
and fell asleep.
My hand wasn't hurt by you either.
I woke up in the middle of the night,
and was startled when I saw you.
So I accidentally sprained it myself.
It has nothing to do with you.
Go sit down quickly.
The food will be ready soon.
Xuanye,
you mentioned last time
your demon transformation was because of the Peerless Bracelet
and your brother.
So this time, could it be...
It's not him.
Before, he just wanted me to
be clear about my identity.
Now that he's achieved his goal,
there's no reason
for him to use that thing again.
You trust him a lot.
Zi Kong is my
half-brother by a different mother.
My mother passed away early.
When I was young,
he was always there to accompany me.
Although he acts recklessly,
he wouldn't really harm me.
Have you finished eating?
I'll go clean up.
Let me do it.
What are you thinking about?
Don't always be so heavy-hearted.
Thinking too much will make you age.
You'll grow white hair again.
What's this?
It's a little Xuanye I embroidered myself.
Isn't it cute?
It's cute.
It's for you.
Xuanye,
what's the Carefree Land like?
Haven't you been there?
I was still young at that time.
Plus, I was so scared then,
busy trying to escape.
I didn't have time to see anything.
Carefree Land
is just a really vast world.
Probably similar to here.
What about your father?
My father?
What kind of person is your father?
My father
is a very powerful person.
He's the leader of the Mystic Panther Clan,
the Guardian King of the Carefree Land.
He's usually very busy.
Except during the grand clan meetings,
I rarely get to see him.
Actually, the Mystic Panther Clan
has always been
the guardians of the Carefree Land since ancient times,
responsible for guarding
the Realm Gate and the Carefree Herb.
If your father is the clan leader,
what about you?
Do you want to be the clan leader?
The clan leader.
It seems impressive just by the way it sounds.
Don't all men want to be officials?
Do you want to?
What exactly are you trying to ask?
I don't know either.
I'm just...
a bit scared.
I'm afraid that as your abilities grow stronger
and you remember more things,
you might
want to go back home one day.
I'm scared
that you'll suddenly leave
and leave me all alone.
Don't be afraid.
No matter what happens,
I will always be with you.
Xuanye,
calm down.
It's me, Banxia.
Xuanye,
it's me, Banxia. Wake up.
Banxia.
Banxia!
I'm fine.
Banxia.
Banxia!
The pass token for the Underground City.
Chief Constable Wen,
we're off duty early today.
Let's go see Xuanye.
Tomorrow is our day off.
Let's go tomorrow.
Chief.
Brother.
I heard that Yanlai Restaurant
has a new dancer
who dances extremely well.
Why don't we go for a drink?
Sure.
You guys go ahead. I'll head back first.
In such a hurry to get home?
Is it because Sima Lingying
is still staying at your place?
Mind your own business.
Get ready for a wedding celebration.
What happened?
How did she get so badly injured?
I need to trouble you
to take care of Banxia for a while.
Where are you going?
I have something to take care of.
If she wakes up,
tell her
to wait for me here.
Can you tell us what it is?
Banxia is seriously injured right now.
Are you sure you want to leave now?
I'm counting on you two.
Xuanye!
[Ganshan Clinic]
Master.
Xuanye,
why are you back?
Uncle,
I've made a decision.
Alright.
Banxia.
Lingying went out to buy some things.
She asked me to remind you
to take your medicine on time.
Thank you.
Did Xuanye say anything else?
Xuanye asked you to rest well and recover.
He'll come back to you once he finished his business.
Don't overthink it.
Xuanye isn't a reckless person.
He must have
his reasons for doing this.
Yes,
he always has his own reasons.
Chief Constable Chu,
could you help me hire a carriage?
I want to return to Nanyang.
Why do you suddenly want to go back to Nanyang?
I've been away for so long.
My family must be worried.
I know
you're angry at Xuanye.
Maybe he'll be back soon.
Why don't you wait for him?
I'm not angry.
I like him so much.
I know what kind of person
he is.
No matter where, I'll still be waiting for him.
I might as well wait at home.
Besides,
it's inconvenient for you
to have me staying at your place.
How is it inconvenient?
Lingying is here,
she can take care of you.
I don't want to trouble you anymore.
[Ganshan Clinic]
Watch where you're going!
Are you blind?
What a coincidence.
We meet again.
What happened to you?
Did you hit a snag?
I have no intention of being your enemy.
Stop following me.
Who's following you?
I have something to ask you.
Did you know that Xuanye left again?
I heard you two are brothers.
You bully your brother so much,
do your parents know?
When did he leave?
I'm not telling you.
Where did he go?
That's what I wanted to ask you.
At first, we thought
you came back to provoke him again.
But seeing you in this state,
it seems you're not capable of that.
I'm very curious.
Who did this to you?
Tell me,
so I can thank them.
What are you looking at?
Even if you want to leave,
there's no need to be in such a hurry.
Sima Lingying went to buy stuff.
Why don't you wait until she returns?
I think it's still early.
Could you wait for her?
Chief Constable Chu,
it's not early anymore.
If we wait a bit longer,
we might as well leave tomorrow.
Tomorrow works too.
How about you leave tomorrow?
Chief Constable Chu.
Youhuang.
Who is this?
This is Physician Jiu's brother,
the other panther demon.
Xuanye.
To suppress your demonic nature,
you even went as far as
forcibly reversing your qi and blood.
This method is extremely dangerous.
Let me tell you,
this is the only time.
You're not allowed to use it again.
I previously
had mastered the method
to control my demon form.
Why now
can't I control it anymore?
I don't know either.
Uncle,
you've lived in the Underground City
for so many years,
often interacting and
and doing business with demons.
Haven't you heard
anything about this?
You should drink some tea first.
I only know
My brother has a secret treasure,
called the Bone Flute.
It can temporarily
make me lose my mind
and lose control of my demon form.
Previously,
he used this method
to force me to reveal my true form.
Xuanye,
if that's the case,
he must be involved in this matter.
How about this?
I'll assign more people
to find him for you.
Thank you for your help, Uncle.
Where's Miss Duan?
She's injured.
Injured by you?
Uncle,
you mentioned a method
to transform from a demon into a human,
does it really exist?
There's no turning back once you've started.
Have you made up your mind?
Why are you here?
Who hurt you?
What does it have to do with you?
Of course it does.
You are Xuanye's brother.
Although you're not friendly to him,
you're still of the same kind.
Your demon powers are strong.
Whoever can hurt you
must be able to hurt him too.
Of course I need to find out.
I don't know them.
There were many of them.
They're all skilled demon hunters.
Their leader
is quite old,
and seems to be in poor health.
Where are they?
The Underground City.
Why did they
do this to you?
Man Ying
must have told you
about my background.
The 12th year is coming.
When the Realm Gate opens,
it will be our chance to return home.
My purpose coming to the human world this time
is to bring him back home.
In 12 years,
the gate only opens once.
How did you come here then?
I have my own way.
But this method has limitations,
only one person can pass through at a time.
When I came out of the Realm Gate,
I noticed something unusual about the pool water at the gate.
After that,
I saw that group of people
bringing in a flower demon,
telling her,
"If you jump into this Bone Washing Pool,
you can wash away your demonic roots
and transform into a human."
What happened to that flower demon?
It's dead.
Then they discovered me.
So I fought with them.
There were too many of them,
and I was also worried about Man Ying,
so I left.
So, this is the reason why
they're hunting you down.
Perhaps.
After that,
they kept tracking me.
I let my guard down for a moment
and fell into their ambush.
Oh no.
What's wrong?
I suddenly remembered
Xuanye's Uncle had previously asked him
if he wanted to be a demon
or a human.
He could choose.
The leader
is Man Ying's Uncle?
Then, could it be...
Are you sure that the Bone Washing Pool
can't turn demons into humans?
Of course.
I saw it with my own eyes.
It seems that old man
wants to trick Man Ying into it too.
No way.
I need to go to the Underground City.
I'll go with you.
Let's go together.
I'll go too.
Wen Jian, you'd better not go.
It's too dangerous.
Besides, the government office needs someone.
You stay here.
If anything happens to us,
you report to My Lord
to have someone come down to rescue us.
We should hurry.
Then let's set off immediately.
Alright.
Okay.
As if lambs to the slaughter.
I'll go with you.
Look at you, acting all capable.
If we are lambs to the slaughter,
who were the ones who tied you up here?
Let's go.